snapstream.com 2008-12-18

# SnapStream: Privacy Policy

Updated February 28, 2007

Thank you for visiting the home of SnapStream Media, Inc. (“SnapStream”).

**1.0 Overarching Commitment**

SnapStream is committed to protecting the privacy of our users’ personal information. The SnapStream Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”), set forth below, provides a detailed description of what information SnapStream currently collects, how SnapStream protects said information, and means for SnapStream users to contact SnapStream concerning collection of their personal information and the Privacy Policy. 

The Privacy Policy covers information collected when using any SnapStream website (“Site”), including but not limited to the SnapStream store (“Store”), Couchville.com ("Couchville"), SnapStream.Net (“.Net”), the SnapStream Forums (“Forums”); SnapStream Beyond TV (“Beyond TV”); SnapStream Beyond Media (“Beyond Media”); SnapStream Firefly PC Remote (“Firefly”); and SnapStream Firefly Mini PC Remote (“Firefly Mini”). The Privacy Policy will be updated when necessary; so, please check here (http://www.snapstream.com/privacy.asp) for future updates or contact SnapStream directly for a copy through the means set forth below in Section 7.0.   

**2.0 Categories of Information**

2.1 “Personally Identifiable Information” means any information that identifies or can be used to identify or contact the user to whom such information pertains. This includes information that is not Personally Identifiable Information but is used in a way that makes the information personally identifiable. Such uses include linking the information with Personally Identifiable Information from other sources, including, but not limited to, name, address, phone number, email address, and credit card information. To the extent unique information (which by itself is not Personally Identifiable Information) such as a personal profile, a unique identifier, or an IP address is associated with Personally Identifiable Information, then such unique information will also be considered Personally Identifiable Information. Personally Identifiable Information does not include information that is collected anonymously (i.e., without identification of the individual user), or demographic information not connected to an identified individual.

2.2 “Non-Personally Identifiable Information” means any information SnapStream collects that cannot be directly linked to an individual user.

**3.0 Information Gathered**

3.1 SnapStream Site: When a user visits our Site, certain Non-Personally Identifiable Information is recorded. SnapStream automatically documents what pages the user visits and for how long, from where the user linked, the user’s IP address, and other technical statistics, none of which is used to personally identify the user. SnapStream collects the data to learn from where Site visitors come, what Site features users use most, and other similar development- and maintenance-related information so that SnapStream can improve service for our users. SnapStream urges the user to read the Google/Urchin Privacy Policy as well, located at <http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacy.html>. 

3.2 SnapStream Store: When a user orders products from the Store, certain Personally Identifiable Information is recorded, including, but not limited to, name, address, phone number, email address, and credit card information. Certain Non-Personally Identifiable Information is also recorded, including, but not limited to IP address, items ordered, and the referring URL. The Store is currently powered by Yahoo!. SnapStream urges the user to read the Yahoo! Privacy Policy as well, located at http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us/.

3.3 Couchville: When a user visits Couchville, certain Non-Personally Identifiable Information is recorded. SnapStream automatically documents what pages the user visits and for how long, from where the user linked, the user’s IP address, and other technical statistics, none of which is used to personally identify the user. SnapStream collects the data to learn from where Couchville visitors come, what Couchville features users use most, and other similar development- and maintenance-related information so that SnapStream can improve service for our users. 

Additionally, when a user creates a personalized line-up in Couchville, Couchville will place a cookie file on the user’s hard drive. Said cookie does not contain any personally identifiable information but does record the zip code and tv service provider provided by the user. Upon the user’s next visit to Couchville, the cookie will be called up, providing a faster, user-specific interface. Cookies can be blocked or removed through your browser features; however, blocking or removing cookies will deny the user customized content delivery.

3.4 SnapStream Beyond TV: When a user uses Beyond TV, certain Non-Personally Identifiable Information is recorded, including but not limited to, whether the user is upgrading from a previous version. Additionally, users are given the option to enable certain advanced features. Should the user choose to enable the advanced features, certain Personally Identifiable Information may be gathered by SnapStream, including, but not limited to user viewing preferences and recording choices and preferences.

3.5 SnapStream Beyond Media: When a user uses Beyond Media, certain non-personally identifiable information is recorded, including but not limited to, what version the user is employing. 

**4.0 Information Disclosure**

4.1 General: Any Personally Identifiable Information SnapStream gathers about users is kept securely for internal SnapStream use only, except for the specific, temporary uses set forth in Section 4.2 below. SnapStream may share aggregated or Non-Personally Identifiable Information with business partners, advertisers, contractors, vendors, or other third parties. Should SnapStream wish to release Personally Identifiable Information to third parties other than when described in this Privacy Policy, SnapStream will request the individual user’s permission first.

4.2 Contractors and Vendors: SnapStream uses contractors to perform certain aspects of SnapStream operations, including but not limited to technical support. Some of these contractors will have temporary access to SnapStream databases of Personally Identifiable Information for specific tasks. SnapStream also uses vendors to perform certain aspects of SnapStream operations, including but not limited to the printing and mailing of feature or service materials, the printing and mailing of rebate checks, and the processing of credit cards. Some of these vendors will have temporary access to SnapStream databases of Personally Identifiable Information for specific tasks. Such contractors and vendors are legally liable for misuse of Personally Identifiable Information. Additionally, SnapStream requires any vendor or contractor to comply with this Privacy Policy and our security measures. 

4.3 Required by Law: SnapStream reserves the right to release any information gathered about users, if refusing to do so would place SnapStream in violation of laws that apply to SnapStream – local, state, federal, and international – including responses to subpoenas. SnapStream also reserves the right to keep confidential information within our records if releasing that information could place SnapStream Media in violation of applicable laws.

**5.0 Information Security**

5.1 Security Employed: SnapStream is committed to keeping all information gathered about users secure against loss, misuse, or alteration by using industry-standard security practices, including restricted access to the data, physically securing the servers storing the data and through regular backups of the database. SnapStream owns the servers that host our Site, and all servers are kept in a high-security co-location facility. 

5.2 Security Disclaimer: SnapStream cannot guarantee the security of the information gathered about users. Even with the high level of security employed by SnapStream, third parties may still circumvent SnapStream security measures to unlawfully access stored Personally Identifiable Information. Any such breaches will be communicated to the affected users as soon as possible after the breach.

**6.0 E-mail Policy**

SnapStream is committed to not adding to our users’ Spam woes. SnapStream will never send users’ e-mail without said user’s consent. Ordering product through SnapStream’s Site, sending e-mail to SnapStream, or contacting SnapStream via the e-mails listed in Section 7.0 implies that the user consents to being contacted by SnapStream via e-mail. Should a SnapStream user not wish to receive e-mail from SnapStream, user may contact SnapStream via the methods in Section 7.0 to request removal from SnapStream mailing lists.

**7.0 Contacting SnapStream**

Any questions regarding the Privacy Policy, requests for removal from SnapStream mailing lists, or updates to your information may be addressed directly to SnapStream via one of the below methods:

In person or via mail:

SnapStream Media, Inc.  
ATTN: Privacy Department  
6730 Long Drive  
Houston, TX 77087  
USA

Via phone: 713.644.6240  
Via fax: 713.644.3215  
Via e-mail: [privacy@snapstream.com](mailto:privacy@snapstream.com)

**8.0 Miscellaneous**

8.1 Amendments to this Privacy Policy: In the event that SnapStream decides to substantially and materially change the manner in which SnapStream treats the information gathered on our users, including but not limited to a change in the way that SnapStream gathers, uses, or discloses Personally Identifiable Information, SnapStream will post such changes on the Site; User’s can change their privacy preferences by following the guidelines in Section 7.0. SnapStream may include or offer new features in SnapStream products in the future. To the extent that any new features may require amendments to this Privacy Policy to describe the treatment of information gathered on our users, those amendments are effective upon notice to the user of the change.

8.2 Entire Agreement: This Privacy Policy supplements and is incorporated into all SnapStream End-User Agreements. This Privacy Policy constitutes the entire agreement, and replaces and supersedes all prior agreements, between the user and SnapStream concerning the subject matter discussed in this Privacy Policy.

**BY USING THE SITE, THE STORE, COUCHVILLE, BEYOND TV, .NET, FORUMS, BEYOND MEDIA, FIREFLY, OR FIREFLY MINI YOU REPRESENT THAT YOU HAVE READ AND UNDERSTOOD THIS ENTIRE PRIVACY POLICY AND YOU AGREE TO ALL THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AS STATED ABOVE.**

* * *

**To view a past version of the Privacy Policy, select a link below:**

  * **Privacy Policy (10/18/2000 \- 3/23/2006)**
  * **Privacy Policy (3/24/2006 \- 2/27/2007)  
**

|
